basementsystems.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Statement by Basement Systems for Customers and Site Visitors

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you enter our website including, but not limited to, ip-address, website you have visited from, searches you have made before coming to our site and any information you provide when signing up for a FREE estimate or newsletter.

**How do we use your information?**  
We pass the information you enter into our contact form to the local dealership who will contact you about the request you made via our web site. We may use your information to follow up about products, services, appointments, etc. and to study user behavior to improve the quality of our web site and services. If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mails from us, please reply to any emails asking to remove you from our list.

**How do we protect visitor information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use "cookies" or "sessions"?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**How do we use "cookies" or "sessions"?**  
Primarily we use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.

Our website uses Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. This means that third-party vendors, including Google will display our ads on sites across the internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together. Additional Adwords features we specifically use include: affinity audiences, custom affinity audiences, in-market audiences, similar audiences and demographic & location targeting. The reason we use these features is to best inform, optimize and serve ads most relevant to you. 

We also use these cookies to receive reports on ad impressions, other uses of ad services & interactions with these ad impressions and how ad services relate to visits to our website. Display Advertising allows us to use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features collect information such as, but not limited to, age, gender and interest categories.

**How do we protect your personally identifiable information**  
We do not facilitate the merging of personally identifiable information (last name, phone address, etc.) with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie. In this way your anonymity is protected. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>. To opt out of Google Analytics tracking entirely visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties certain personally identifiable information (including your last name, house number, street name, phone number and email address) unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. 

The term "outside parties" does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves or others.

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Changes to our policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This Privacy Policy was last updated May 26, 2015.

**We want to hear from you.**  
Any Questions, Comments or Suggestions?  

Phone: 1-800-638-7048

**Visit us or mail us:**  
Basement Systems, Inc.  
60 Silvermine Rd  
Seymour, CT 06483

Looking for a price? Get a no cost, no obligation [free estimate](http://www.basementsystems.com/free-estimate.html).
